http://www.guifx.com/privacy-terms

Privacy Policy
Guifx has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website.
IP Addresses and Cookies
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our servers, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address and cookie file is used to help identify you and your personal profile, track shopping cart items, and track your access via .htaccess requests, where applicable.
Personal Information
Our site uses a variety of feedback and/or registration forms, order forms, online survey forms, and submission forms which require users to give us contact information (like name and email address). The user's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary. Contact information from these forms may also be used to send information about our company and scheduled events, merchandise specials, contests, or other information relating to Guifx and its strategic partners. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.
Links
This site contains links to other sites. Guifx is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
Public Forums
This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.
Security
This site employs security measures to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.
Subscription Mailing List
If you have subscribed to our mailing list and now wish to remove yourself from it, you may do so via the included unsubscribe link located inside all of our sent email correspondence.
Choice/Opt-Out
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service and cancel their subscriptions.
Correct/Update
This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided.
Contacting the Web Site
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact us.
Terms of Service
PLEASE READ THE FOLLOWING CONDITIONS OF USE AND DISCLAIMER CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS WEB SITE (this "SITE"). By accessing or using this site, you agree to these terms of use. If you do not agree to these terms you may not use this site.
Copyright
All site design, text, graphics, interfaces, and the selection and arrangements thereof are Copyright © 2000-2016, Guifx, LLC. ALL RIGHTS RESERVED. Permission is granted to electronically copy and to print hard copy portions of this site for the sole purpose of placing an order with Guifx or using this site as a shopping resource. Any other use of materials on this site, including reproduction for purposes other than those noted above, modification, distribution, or republication, without prior written permission of Guifx is strictly prohibited.
Trademarks
Guifx and the Guifx logo are Trademark(s) of Guifx, LLC. All rights reserved. All trademarks, service marks, and trade names (collectively the "Marks") are proprietary to Guifx or other respective owners that have granted Guifx the right and license to use such Marks.
Disclaimer
THE INFORMATION, SERVICES, PRODUCTS, AND MATERIALS CONTAINED IN THIS SITE, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, TEXT, GRAPHICS, AND LINKS, ARE PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" BASIS WITH NO WARRANTY. TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY THE LAW, GUIFX DISCLAIMS ALL REPRESENTATIONS AND WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, WITH RESPECT TO SUCH INFORMATION, SERVICES, PRODUCTS, AND MATERIALS, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, TITLE, NONINFRINGEMENT, FREEDOM FROM COMPUTER VIRUS, AND IMPLIED, WARRANTIES ARISING FROM COURSE OF DEALING OR COURSE OF PERFORMANCE. IN ADDITION, GUIFX DOES NOT REPRESENT OR WARRANT THAT THE INFORMATION ACCESSIBLE VIA THIS SITE IS ACCURATE, COMPLETE OR CURRENT. PRICE AND AVAILABILITY INFORMATION IS SUBJECT TO CHANGE WITHOUT NOTICE.
Limitation on Liability
IN NO EVENT SHALL GUIFX BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL, PUNITIVE, INCIDENTAL, EXEMPLARY OR CONSEQUENTIAL, DAMAGES, OR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER, EVEN IF GUIFX HAS BEEN PREVIOUSLY ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES, WHETHER IN AN ACTION UNDER CONTRACT, NEGLIGENCE, OR ANY OTHER THEORY, ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE USE, INABILITY TO USE, OR PERFORMANCE OF THE INFORMATION, SERVICES, PRODUCTS, AND MATERIALS AVAILABLE FROM THIS SITE. THESE LIMITATIONS SHALL APPLY NOTWITHSTANDING ANY FAILURE OF ESSENTIAL PURPOSE OF ANY LIMITED REMEDY. BECAUSE SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW LIMITATIONS ON HOW LONG AN IMPLIED WARRANTY LASTS, OR THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES, THE ABOVE LIMITATIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.
External Sites
This site may contain links or advertisements to other sites on the Internet that are owned and operated by third party vendors and other third parties (the "External Sites"). You acknowledge that Guifx is not responsible for the availability of, or the content located on or through, any External Site. You should contact the site administrator or Webmaster for those External Sites if you have any concerns regarding such links or the content located on such External Sites.
In such…
You will probably notice that we have linked our site to other Web sites. You should understand that this does not mean that we have looked at all these sites, that we have checked their content, or that we endorse them. We disclaim any responsibility if some site you link to has material on it that offends you in any way.
Submissions
All submissions used by Guifx will be available for syndication by us to our affiliate sites. This is a free service we provide to affiliate sites and helps promote our Web site as well as your submissions. We do not receive any royalties for syndication and therefore Guifx is NOT offering payout for submissions or staff writing. By submitting your content, photos, art, and other intellectual property to Guifx, you grant Guifx the right to use and / or syndicate such submitted materials.
Our Addresses
http://www.guifx.com
Copyright © 2000-2016 Guifx, LLC
Copyright © 2000 -
Guifx, LLC. All rights reserved.
|
Privacy Policy
|
Terms of Service
Keep in touch!
